except better we get some quality issues
with the previous one I feel sometimes
periscope doesn't like try to up
bandwidth enough again may add a nursing
so what your people join so quickly but
it's a quality better dad tell me is a
quality about it by the way I can go to
Twitter or get Jack let's go to Twitter
how much better guy shave know either
you guys know instagrams facebook bros
but you know what new respect from Mark
Zuckerberg um okay cool I'm glad it's
better is it much better I'd say well
that's so good okay nobody can complain
right now you have broken now you have
broken stuff flip the orientation yes if
you're using a neo case you are
all right kissing screen now that's Jeff
whatever make sure it's good if you've
joined the Wi-Fi Twitter's interface
saves the bit right that's so bad yeah
look we're watching myself on the scope
II that's pretty good I don't think we
can complain about that all right cool
let's go through the code um this is 0
for 4 are the biggest news is your yawns
are flipped if you don't have something
flipped you're gonna be very sad I see
you know we have the neo to Aeon trading
program ridge line support thanks to
energy optional front camera recording
increased acceleration the new
onboarding screen didn't make it in and
Neos are no longer supported so maybe we
should put a sad face next to that one
but it is sad so maybe we'll check it
with a sad face all right cool this is
the diff we added in a bunch of crap in
cereal car Kathy Eppie none of that
should matter never to you guys so you
can see the screen better cereal car
caffeine pee we added in a bunch of
crappy air I'm gonna rotate you back
this is too hard
front cameras are now recorded we have a
third MPC you guys aren't really using
that and on the whip thatis we added in
the fingerprint for the bolt so we've
pulled the voltage or our internal code
we're thinking about buying a GM next
week and doing the port record front is
now an option so this is just an option
and our usual options interface I
refactored the fingerprinting stuff bit
so if you guys remember this is what it
used to be to add a new car I don't have
like all these like try caches and stuff
so I just
refactor that to that what about bolt
yes the part the boldest of ACC it only
has L casts where do you store all these
cars we let the employees drive them you
guys tell us to worry about any of that
you're not using angle control
know why that wasn't in there I'm not
really understanding why that changes in
there you guys have to worry about that
so notice the orientation is no longer
three it's now one the version was
bumped to 0 for 4
he used to be 0.32 now it's over for
bunch of improvements to the vision
stream API that just clean up better we
added a streaming for the front camera
so it can be recorded and oh we've
changed it um so it's not just always
keep hands on wheel anymore
it's always keeping hands on wheel and
eyes on the road uh just you know pay
attention recall my buddies gonna be
here in 30 minutes it's perfect timing
if you clean up to the MPC don't use
divide the vines are evil we don't use
divides its yeah a lot of a path right
in Python I'm since it generated code
I'm very bad oh the uploader change um I
mention that Mia release notes oh I
should mention that the release notes oh
okay I'll make sure to add that um so
the upload are no longer uploads over
cellular if you turn off upload routes
over cellular so you guys can put a sim
card in your eons and they won't waste
tons of data anymore not that it's a
waste but if you don't have unlimited
data and now should use open pilots
should use like like a Megan our I'm so
that should kind of be no problem the
flippin Aang that's therein manager yeah
t-mobile unlimited data that's where
it's at um so note that 0 here record
front is disabled by default so it's
opt-in it's not opt out evident in code
ID acts added a new maneuver to the
tests a couple bug fixes to the UI and
the new updater okay yeah so the updater
is going to
ask you before it installs an update we
learn we improve every day we get better
we drive all right scobie's that's been
zero for for um any questions don't
limit any audible for old cars I don't
care
oh you mean even New Model T whoa whoa
whoa whoa don't want me to introduce you
to the map team last night can you see
the front video so we don't actually way
to do that we'll see what we are going
to launch first is an attention report
that you'll be able to download for your
routes the third video is completely
optional don't opt in if you don't feel
comfortable doing it what does NPC NPCs
model predictive control
no no world war three guys though
though I do have seven days of food and
water in my basement so maybe that's why
I'm a little less worried than the rest
of you it sucks you know but just just
live your life and try to do your best
at whatever you do unless it's bothering
people in the above all anybody that
kind of sucks additional point five
common points at release yep that's
already in the back end I believe we're
also the infrastructure engineer
starting Monday so he wants to make
himself known to you guys but if he does
what time it's gonna drop them like an
hour we're gonna wait for Andy to do
something and we gotta wait for Ricardo
to do the final test and if those two
things are good then we would
orientation Three's old code orientation
one is new code
alright scobie's thanks for joining
I think through the night throw at the
release I'm sure you guys do too but the
release will go out about 30 minutes
we'll tweet about it on Twitter
0:44 is gonna be nice and we're gonna
just we'll just going into valve but
we're trying to push that to release you
have a good weekend to spell by 32
ladies